Guide to the Stanford University, Planning Office, Records SC0486
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2005-116
  - Administrative Space Planning 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - San Mateo County Zoning 1978 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Ford Center 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - International Studies Institute 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Main Quad 1981 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Roads 1978-79 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Serra Buildings 1989 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Interfaith Chapel 1985 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Materials Recovery Facility 1987 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - GSB Expansion 1988 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Child Care Center - Arboretum 1987 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Long Term Land Use Group 1985 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Legislation 1975 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lighting Master Plan 1980 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Parking 1979 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Personal Safety Committee 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Academic Resources Center 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Applied Physics - Ginzton Lab 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Tanner Fountain 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - SRI/Stanford Seismic Test Facility 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Committee 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1100 Welch Road housing 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Humanities Center Annex, Van Patten House 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Law School Student Center 1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - CSLI [Center for the Study of Language and Information] 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - CSLI 1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Cantor Sculpture Garden 1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Borehole Geophysics Test Facility 1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Parking Structure I 1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Math Corner Courtyard 1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Lasuen Mall / Mayfield to Braun 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Parking lot at Galvez/Serra 1983 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Roth Way Extension 1984-86 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Pasteur Drive South Realignment 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Mayfield Ave reconstruction 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Electioneer Road 1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Campus Drive/Serra Street 1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hacienda Area 1985 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Club 1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Storage of Fill Material 1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Landscaping Frenchmen's Hill 1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Campus Properties Status Report 1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Signs Campus 1987 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Biological Sciences Expansion 1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Campus Lighting 1987 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Parking Structure II (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Alumni/Development 1.1 Form I/Proposals/Schedule/ Budget 1.0 Project Administration (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Alumni/Development 1.2 contracts 1.0 Project Administration (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Alumni/Development 1.3 Correspondence 1.0 Project Administration (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Alumni/Development 1.4 Meeting Minutes 1.0 Project Administration (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Alumni/Development 2.2 General (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Alumni/Development 2.3 Building and Site Info. 2.0 Project Information (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Alumni/Development 2.1 Preliminary Space Need Summary 2.0 Project Information (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Alumni/Development 2.5 Feasibility Study (1992) 2.0 Project Information (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Lagunita Court Seismic (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - DAPER - Master Plan (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - DAPER - Master Plan (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - GSB Link (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Serra Mall Sculpture (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Serra Mall Outdoor Art (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Parking Structure IV - PS IV (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Parking Structure 4 1.1 General 1.0 Planning and programming (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Parking Structure 4 1.2 Formulation 1.0 Planning and programming (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Parking Structure 4 1.3 Budget/Cost Estimates 1.0 Planning and programming (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Parking Structure 4 1.3 Budget/Cost Estimates 1.0 Planning and programming (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Parking Structure 4 2.1 General 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Parking Structure 4 2.2 Meetings 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Parking Structure 4 2.3 Correspondence 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Parking Structure 4 3.1 General 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Serra Grove (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Stadium Elevator (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - DAPER - Promenades (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - CIS Terrace (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - DAPER - DeGuerre Pool Site (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Cobb Track/Angell Field Bleachers (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Stadium - Scoreboard Replacement (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Huston House 2.1 General 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Huston House 2.2 FEMA/ Section 106 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Huston House 3.1 General 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Huston House 3.1 General 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Huston House 3.2 Construction Meeting Minutes 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Huston House 4.1 General 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Housing Bike Rack (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Sunken Diamond Lights (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Electioneer Road Parking (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Searsville Road Parking (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Wilbur Lot Reconfiguration (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Track House Lot (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Memorial Auditorium Lot (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Hopkins Marine Station Lab Building (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Hopkins Marine Station Lab Building (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 1.1 Management Proposals - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 2.3 General: 1995 - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 1.3 General: 1/94 - 8/94 - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 3.2 Sequoia Hall Demolition - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 1.4 General: 9/94 - 2/95 - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 1.2 Architect Proposals - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - SEQ Tour (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 2.1 Initial Study (Enviornmental Assessment) - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 2.2 Steering Committee - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 3.1 Construction and Procurement - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 4.2 General - 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Science and Engineering Quad - 4.1 Model Photographs - 4.0 Graphics and Materials (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - SEQ Trees (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - SEQ Electrical Engineering (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - SEQ HEPL Room 146 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - SEQ Lab for Advanced Materials (LAM) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - SEQ McCullough Remodel (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 1.1 General 1990-93 - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 1.2 General 1994-96 - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1 Approvals - 2.0 Design and Documentation - (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.2 Project Management - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.2.1 WCC Contract - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.2.2 WCC Invoices - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.2.3 Schedule - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.3 Correspondence - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.3.1 Internal Correspondence - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.3.2 To/from Woodward-Clyde Consultants - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.3.3 To/from Santa Clara County - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.3.4 To/from others - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.4.1 Health Risk and Odor Assessment - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.4.2 ASA (Environmental Information Form) - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.4.3 ASA Conditions of Approval - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.4.4 Media Releases - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.1.4.5 Reference Materials - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 2.2 Other Design and Documentation Activities - 2.0 Design and Documentation (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - Architectural and Engineering Requirements June 3, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - Design Report 1997 and Working Session 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - Miscellaneous items 1994-98 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research (CCSR) - Project History, by Nova Partners, Inc. 1999 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - SEQ Quad and Connective Elements - (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - SEQ Quad and Connective Elements - 1.1 General - Bike Circulation (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - SEQ Quad and Connective Elements - 2.1 General - Generators (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - SEQ Quad and Connective Elements - 3.1 General - Pavilion & Fountain Arcades (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - SEQ Regional Teaching Facility (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - SEQ Statistics (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - SEQ Utilities (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - SEQ South Service Road (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - SEQ Regional Teaching Facility - Levolor samples (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Manzanita 2 [NOT RECEIVED IN ACCESSION] (Box 11)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 1.1 Feasibility Study - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 1.2 General 1988-1990 - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 1.3 General 1991 - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 1.4 General 1992 - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 1.5 General 1993 - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 2.1 General 1993 - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 2.2 General 1994 - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 3.1 General 1994 - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 3.2 General 1995 - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 3.3 General 1996 - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - CIS Extension (CISX) - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Gates Computer Science Building - 1.1 General 1989-1991 - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Gates Computer Science Building - 1.2 General 1992 - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Gates Computer Science Building - 2.1 General 1992 - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Gates Computer Science Building - 2.2 General 1993 - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Gates Computer Science Building - 2.3 General 1994 - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Gates Computer Science Building - 3.1 General 1994 - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Gates Computer Science Building - 3.2 General 1995 - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Gates Computer Science Building - 3.3 General 1996 - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Gates Computer Science Building - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Sand Hill Road - 2.2 Strategy (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Sand Hill Road - 2.2.1 Strategic Planning Group/Lands Plan (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Sand Hill Road - 2.4 Project Costing (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.4 To/from others (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.5 Internal Stanford communication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.7 Lawsuit - 3.0 Correspondence and Communications (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.3.1 BKE (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.3.4 Kosmot and Associates (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.3.5 McCutchen Doyle Brown & Enersen (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.3.6 Others (SWA, BAR, TSG) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.2.1 Menlo Park (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.2.3a Cal Trans (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.2.4 Santa Clara County (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.1 City of Palo Alto (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.1.1 ARB (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Sand Hill Road - 3.1.3 City Council (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.1.1 Stanford West Apartments (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.1.2 Stanford West Seniors Housing (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.2 Transportation (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.2.1 Modeling runs/circulation patterns (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.2.2 Intersection design/eyebrows/details (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.2.3 Alternative modes (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.2.4 Population and Growth Assumptions (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.2.5 Parking (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.3.1 Creek/riparian (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.3.2 Trees (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.4 Archaeology (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.5 Market Study (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Sand Hill Road - 4.6 Utilities/infrastructure (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Sand Hill Road - 5.1 Community Outreach Preparation (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Sand Hill Road - 5.2 Community Outreach Workshop Materials (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Sand Hill Road - 5.3 Community with the public and agencies (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Sand Hill Road - 5.5 Research for community education (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Sand Hill Road - 5.6 Stanford West Brochure (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Sand Hill Road - 6.1 Background (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Sand Hill Road - 6.2 Notice of Preparation and Comments (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Sand Hill Road - 6.3 Scoping of Materials and Comments (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Sand Hill Road - 6.7 Public hearing materials and comments (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Sand Hill Road - 6.9 Findings/mitigation monitoring plan (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Sand Hill Road - 6.10 Lawsuit - 6.0 Environmental Impact Report (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Sand Hill Road - 6.10 Lawsuit - (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Sand Hill Road - 7.0 Construction and Occupancy (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Vision Center at Veterans Hospital - 1.1 Vision, Expectations, and Development - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Vision Center at Veterans Hospital - 1.2 Agreements and Approvals - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Vision Center at Veterans Hospital - 1.3 Environmental Issues, Studies, and Reports - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Vision Center at Veterans Hospital - 1.4 Regulations - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Vision Center at Veterans Hospital - 1.5 RFP Items - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Vision Center at Veterans Hospital - 1.6 Meetings - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Vision Center at Veterans Hospital - 1.7 Correspondence - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Vision Center at Veterans Hospital - 1.8 Graphics - 1.0 Planning and Programming (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Library Tech Services [EMPTY] - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 13)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner [EMPTY] - 1.13 Internal Correspondence - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 13)
  - Serra Mall Phase I - 1.1 General - 1.0 General (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Serra Mall Phase I - 1.2 Plans and Materials - 1.0 General - (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Serra Mall Phase I - 2.1 1990-1993 - 2.0 Chronological File (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Serra Mall Phase I - 2.2 1994 Jan - Sept - 2.0 Chronological File - (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Serra Mall Phase I - 2.3 1994 Oct - Dec - 2.0 Chronological File (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Serra Mall Phase I - 2.5 1995 March - Dec - 2.0 Chronological File (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Serra Mall Phase I - 2.4 1995 Jan - Feb - 2.0 Chronological File (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Serra Mall Phase I - 2.6 1996 - 2.0 Chronological File (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - SEQ - Statistics/Regional Facilities Building (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - ESF - Annex (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Bonair Stores (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - DAPER - Softball Diamond (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Library Tech Services - 1.1 General - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Library Tech Services - 2.1 General - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Library Tech Services - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Library Tech Services - (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 1.10 Tanner Leddy Maytum Stacy - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 1.12 Other Consultants Correspondence - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 1.4 Project costing/budget - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 1.14 Meeting Notes - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 1.15 BoT Presentation Materials - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 1.18 Trees - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 1.19 Transit/bikes - 1.0 Planning & Programming (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - Assorted documents (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 2.1 Design guidelines - program materials - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 2.2 Schematic Design - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 2.3 Parking lot requirements and design - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 2.4 Design changes - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 2.5 Design Development - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 2.6 Site and foundation permit - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 2.7 Construction Documents - 2.0 Design & Documentation (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - Project Program Draft, Nov. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 3.1 General - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 3.2 Construction Minutes - 3.0 Construction & Occupancy (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Grad Housing at Governor's Corner - 4.1 General - 4.0 Graphics & Materials (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - DAPER - Tennis Stadium 1.1 General 1.0 Planning and programming (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - DAPER - Tennis Stadium [untitled folder] (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - DAPER - Tennis Stadium 2.1 General 2.0 Design and documentation (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - DAPER - Tennis Stadium 3.1 General 3.0 Construction and occupancy (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Margaret Jacks Hall 1.1 General 1.0 Planning and programming (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Margaret Jacks Hall 2.1 General 1.0 Design and documentation (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 2.1 Consultant selection process (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 2.2 Schedule (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 2.3.1 Thomas Reid Associates (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 2.3.2 Center for Conservation Bio (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 2.3.3 Balance hydrologics (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 2.4 Costing (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 2.5 Request for funding (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 2.6 Expenditure Statements (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.1 Internal Communications 92-93 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.2 Internal communications 94 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.3 to/from TRA (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.4 to/from CDFG, USFWS, SCC (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.5 to/fromCenter for Conserv. Bio (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.6 to/from Balance Hydrologics (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.7 Steering committee notes (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.8 Meeting notes (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.9 Newspaper articles (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 3.10 Other correspondence (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 4.1 Other Salamander studies (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 4.2 Regulations (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 5.1 Field results (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 5.2 Other research (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation 5.3 Draft Conservation Agreement (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation Agreement - CTSCA 5.4 Bonfire Analysis 5.0 Results (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - California Tiger Salamander Conservation Agreement - CTSCA 5.5 Signed Management Agreement 5.0 Results (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Art Gallery/Cummings Art Building (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - DAPER - Cobb Track & Angell Field (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Bonair Space Study 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bonair Space Study 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Comm. Outreach & Awareness Plan for Const. Act. 1997 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Comm. Outreach & Awareness Plan for Const. Act. 1997 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Littlefield Center Extension 1996-97 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Littlefield Center Extension 1997-99 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Littlefield Center Extension 1997-99 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Littlefield Center Extension 1997 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Bonair Space Study: 2 volume report " Bonair Siding Facilties Analysis and Pre-Space Planning Study, Sept. 1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bonair Space Study: binder labeled " Stores" (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Littlefield Center Extension 2.1 General 2.0 Design and documentation (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Littlefield Center Extension 2.1 General 2.0 Design and documentation (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Littlefield Center Extension [unlabelled folder] (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Littlefield Center Extension [unlabelled folder] (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Littlefield Center Extension 3.1 General 3.0 Construction and occupancy (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Littlefield Center Extension 4.1 General 4.0 Graphics and materials (Box 16, Folder 6)